khaleejtimes.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy - News | Khaleej Times

Khaleej Times is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Khaleej Times Web site (www.khaleejtimes.com) and governs data collection and usage. By using the Khaleej Times website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.  
   
**Collection of your Personal Information**  
   
Khaleej Times collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number.  
   
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Khaleej Times. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Khaleej Times for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Khaleej Times Web site.  
   
**Use of your Personal Information**  
   
Khaleej Times collects and uses your personal information to operate the Khaleej Times Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Khaleej Times also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Khaleej Times and its affiliates. Khaleej Times may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. Khaleej Times does not sell, rent or lease its visitor lists to third parties.  
   
Khaleej Times may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Khaleej Times keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Khaleej Times, in order to determine what Khaleej Times services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Khaleej Times to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.  
   
**Use of Cookies**  
   
The Khaleej Times Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.  
   
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Khaleej Times pages or services, a cookie helps Khaleej Times to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.  
   
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Khaleej Times services or Web sites you visit.  
   
**Third Party Cookies**  
   
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.  
   
**Newsletters**  
   
They can choose to not receive these messages by using the “one-click” opt out/ unsubscribe option available at the bottom of every newsletter.  
   
**Security of your Personal Information**  
   
Khaleej Times secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Khaleej Times secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.  
   
**Changes to this Statement**  
   
Khaleej Times will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Khaleej Times encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Khaleej Times is protecting your information.  
   
**Contact Information**  
   
Khaleej Times welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. For any questions or clarification please contact us at  
   
Head Office, Al Quoz Industrial Area 1, Dubai  
P.O. Box 11243,   
Tel: 04-3383535,   
Fax: 04-3383345   
E-mail: ktimes@emirates.net.ae  

#### Contact Information

Khaleej Times welcomes your comments   
regarding this Statement of Privacy.  
For any questions or clarification  
please contact us or call us at +97143383535
